Hi guys, and welcome back to part 8.3.
We're gonna be talking about adding titles, effects, and overlays.
So in the previous, uh, tutorial,
we basically did our assembly and our timeline and put together our story
according to our script. Um,
one thing that I forgot to mention in the previous one was, uh,
determining what was the style of the video. Um, but because, you know,
as as, as you can tell by the footage, it was U G C, but, um, in this,
uh, portion of the editing segment, we are gonna be, uh,
dialing in the titles, effects and overlays, and that will require us to be,
uh, specific about the actual ad styles. So, uh, just as a reminder, uh,
in this part of the editing stage, this is when we start to spice up our video.
You start to make it look and feel really cool. Um,
I think this makes a huge difference in the quality of your video and as well
as like the professionalism. You can tell when an editor is tight,
when they have very clean titles, clean overlays, and,
and very intentional effects.
Sometimes editors will just use random mass effects that don't actually add to
the video. So you wanna avoid that as much as possible.
And we'll also add some overlays here from Ads Orx, uh,
to show you how we can actually improve, uh, the speed at which we do things.
So that's gonna be really nice.
So next thing that we have to do is determine, okay, out of the, the,
the five different, actually this is five, this should be,
I don't know why this is four, uh, that guess must be a typo. Uh,
the five different ad styles, which one are we gonna be going for?
Obviously we shot that content with an iPhone and it was all in one shoot.
It wasn't necessarily, uh, a, uh, compilation of shoots from different, uh,
different U G C creators, and it wasn't done in the studio.
So I'm gonna go with the U G C, uh, style, right?
So when I'm gonna do U G C, I wanna make sure it looks U G C, all right?
And how I do that is I always start by getting inspiration
from other videos out there existing on the marketplace, okay? Um,
and one place I like to go is using foreplay.
And this is one of the most advanced ad research tools
ad saving tools ever to exist. And I, I, I,
I know the founder personally, he, Zach,
he's built an incredible platform where you can find inspiration and,
you know, research ads and save ads.
And I'll share with you guys a link to this where you guys can sign up.
And also,
I've created my own different boards for different styles of
videos and different niches. But it's incredible, man,
and you will never run out of inspiration with using foreplay, um,
because the traditional way of doing things is just so over, it's just so wonky,
it doesn't work, and it's so, you know, it's a mess.
But using foreplay is fantastic. So this is one place that I like to start,
but, um, I see a A U G C ad real, like right there and then,
so let's just watch it while
Your hair looks greasy too quickly. One,
you are not emulsifying your shampoo enough. All
Right? Uh, just bef, you know, before we watch the whole rest of the video,
I can already tell, uh, what these, you know, titles are gonna be, right.
These are, these look very, what's it called, um,
native to TikTok and Instagram. So they're using the background,
they're using the stroke over that. Um, and, and yeah,
it's pretty straightforward there. Now,
another example that I wanna share, because we actually,
I actually sorted out some examples from here is, let me just pull some up.
Okay? I'm just gonna use this as an example.
Yes,
I would say this is actually better of an example because it is weight loss.
So let's have a look at this.
Found makes, getting my prescription weight loss medication fast and easy.
I took the quiz and I got a personalized treatment plan,
and I get one-on-one access to a medical doctor to ensure my medication matches
my biology.
All right? So what I'm looking at from a design standpoint,
titles and captions and overlays. We've got a zoom in here. Uh,
we've got the titles up top,
and on the bottom it looks like branded colors.
So that's something that we can embed into this video when it gets into the
actual voiceover part, uh, or the testimonial. Um, it looks like we're,
we're trying to emulate the TikTok style format,
but I can always tell when it's not native to TikTok is when there's no curved
line here. And I think only a trained eye can un really understand that. But,
um, our ads orx templates already have the curved line embedded into them,
so that's one less step for you to do,
and you can make it look way more organic than that.
So it looks pretty straightforward. Um, you know,
it looks like she changed the, the, the editor changed the colors here,
but there's nothing too complex in the style. And then lastly,
you've got a nice little call to action, um,
end screen there with the brand and the color. So cool,
I will run with that example. Um,
so let's just jump right into it. All right, so we,
let's go back into our premier timeline. And
I know we have a script here. I know we have some titles already pre, um,
pre-made. So let's just go back here. I know I have some better ones. Um,
All right, I am just gonna make one up because, uh,
this is the clients and I feel like wait list is good for you,
bad for business, most wait very long for a, uh,
for a headline. So first and foremost, I'm gonna work with the hook.
Uh, it's the most important part,
and once I establish the foundation on the hook,
then I can just copy and paste everything over.
But one thing that I really love doing in hooks is
adding a zoom in. Okay? So you can do this two ways.
You can have an automated zoom in, which I have, if I type it,
if I go to my effects and I type in Zoom, or a scale, actually,
I have, um, these fake camera movements,
which I'll include the presets, uh, in this, in this video.
But if I type in scale, it's automated, right, right there,
and I can find a bezier one, which it will give it like kind of a, uh, uh,
it'll, it'll speed it up a little bit versus linear, uh, I, I,
I think linear will be fine.
And this basically goes from 100 to 110% in the scale.
So you don't have to go into the effects controls and actually do it manually.
Sometimes you can do that, or sometimes it's necessary to do that.
And I do that quite often. But for an, an easy clip like this, you know,
adding an automated preset, it just saves so much time. So click in that,
click that, drag it on, and let's preview that. Boom.
Okay, I'm gonna undo that just because I wanna see if, uh, if,
if 1, 1 50 is more intense. So let's try that.
Yeah, I kind of like that more because it's just, you know,
there's more going on and you're, you're seeing more of his eyeballs.
So yeah, let's roll with that.
Okay, next thing I want to add are titles.
So depending on your copywriter, if you wrote the titles,
if you know what headlines work really well for you, um,
you're gonna place that here. All right, so the, the title on a hook is,
is so, so important. It's going to change the performance of your ad.
We always like to test like 10 different titles, 10 different headlines, um,
you know, 10 different headlines with one scroll stopper,
and then find the winning headline and then test out different scroll stoppers.
So it's like you find the right messaging. So there you can do this two ways.
All right, so at,
because you're an ads or X customer or student, so to speak, um,
you're blessed with having templates. So let's just roll with a template here,
and I'm gonna type in TikTok. All right?
And so we have a lot of different styles. We have a few styles.
We just came out with a new one where you can actually drag the emoji into
the title. So, uh, I'm gonna use titles three,
and I'm just gonna drag that onto my timeline and boom,
I'm just gonna, for the sake of the video, just trim that here.
So I don't have any of that excess.
I'm gonna zoom in just so I can see a little bit more clearly. And, alright,
so using this title, um, right now it's pretty bare and that's fine.
What I wanna do is just shut everything off. Okay? So I wanna go in here,
take off, um, on and off feature.
And I just want to keep two lines. Let's see, two lines.
Cool. Alright,
so one thing that I want to do ahead of time is actually change the
text tracking to zero. 'cause right now on by default it's at 68.
So that's the spacing in between the text. And obviously you can,
you can change that here as much as you want, but I like to keep that at zero.
So it reduces the amount of space, um, the brand. Actually,
I'm not sure what font they use. But for this,
lemme just go to their site really quick and see if there's anything, uh,
yeah, let's see.
Right click Inspect and we might be able to pick it up here.
Tail went. Source, source Sands Pro. Okay. Source Sands Pro.
I might have that font. I might not. If not, it's not a big deal.
Source source, I have source code, but all right,
I'm just gonna go with my favorite font, proNova. Alright,
so let's go back to the example and have a quick look at it
so we can get a little bit of a, uh, little bit of inspo. All right,
I lost 60 pounds with found. Let's just copy that.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless.
And then add that little testimonial thing at the bottom.
So right off the bat, I know we have, um,
some brand colors that they like. So let's,
let's get those brand colors in first. Okay,
so this is the actual product itself.
Obviously we probably could have done this beforehand, but, um, you know,
that's part of the, the due diligence process is doing your, your research.
So we've got a lot of colors here. Um, one thing that I'll do is, um,
let's say there's two ways of doing this.
If you wanted to extract the brand colors. One is, uh, you know,
taking a screenshot of this entire thing, then dragging it into your timeline,
and then using the eyedropper tool.
If you don't already have an eyedropper tool as a, uh, shortcut in your browser,
definitely recommend doing that. Uh, it saves a ton of time.
So I'm actually gonna use that and pick a color here.
It looks like we got this dark blue, which is a nice one.
I'm gonna take this hex color,
go back to my premiere and I'm gonna go into my,
my graphics folder. And I'm gonna create a new item.
I'm gonna do a color mat, okay? And I'm going to click okay,
and I'm gonna paste this into there. I'm gonna call this dark blue.
Okay? Now that I have that, I'm gonna do the same for the other colors.
So we've got pick a color from the page, we've got this light blue,
it's like a C foam green, same thing here. Color mat
C green. And let's do one more of this.
Light blue. Looks like there's a light blue going on. Okay.
All right,
for some reason I can't touch this over here,
so I'm just gonna find something else.
So it looks like 6 4 9 cc, 4 6 4 9 cc four, okay,
I
6, 6, 4 9,
cc four. Okay, great. Light blue.
Now I've got all the brand colors. Fantastic.
Now I can pull on that anytime I need it.
So let's do the same as that video.
What was it? I lost 60 pounds with weightless. Okay,
so in this template, what's really great about this is I can just go in here.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless
and I think it's like that.
Alright, now it's up there.
Lemme just double check the product name.
I know I should know this stuff, but when you move so fast,
sometimes you don't have time. All right, so there is a, uh,
let just copy and paste this text if I can.
There it is, because I want that, I want the TM symbol in there.
I know that I, I'm pretty sure that if you do command
is that command R, there's a tmm symbol,
but yeah, I think it's, I think it's, um,
alt op or option two or alt alt two.
Cool. Okay, so you see these two little dots right here.
Those are actually placeholders for emojis and, um,
you can remove those, but you can also add them later on,
which is like super cool. And I'll show you how to do that in a second. Um,
but I'm actually gonna remove line two 'cause I don't think I need it. Uh,
let's see what we got going on here.
So let's see what this looks like with the font size a little bigger.
And now let's Change the color.
Let's do that dark blue background.
And let's go down here and go to the box color and boom,
get the dark blue. Hey,
weird. I don't know why that's doing that.
Let me just pull that hex color. Then I think it might be because I'm,
I'm recording on Loom and it's giving me that yellow bar.
So next I'm going to change the text color to white.
So it has that brand look cool. All right,
I lost 60 pounds with weightless, and then
he's got Jessica real found client.
So we'll do something like that as well.
So I'm just gonna hit option.
And I think that could be alt on pc, but option drag,
you're gonna duplicate that layer right above it. Okay?
And next I'm going to move this, I'm gonna move this, uh, down.
I can do that two ways. I can do the y position right here, um,
which, yeah, there it is. I can do y position here,
or I can go over into the position and the effects controls right here and move
it there. So it really is your preference. Um,
and let's now change,
we'll call him Matt, real wait
List
User. Cool.
All right.
Yeah. So That's, that's looking better.
I'm not like in love with it. I feel like because it's 16 by,
or it's nine by 16, it kind of looks, kind of, looks like,
I feel like these could be bigger in my, my opinion. Um,
so what I will do is actually break this into two lines.
So I'll cut this. All right, I lost 60 pounds,
and then I'm gonna add a second line, and I'm gonna do with weightless,
I'm gonna remove the, the emojis and
I'm gonna increase the font size. That way it's just like a little,
just like bigger. And I don't know, I don't know.
I feel like it blends in a little bit too much with his shirt. So,
you know, obviously because this is a hook, you know,
you don't wanna sacrifice brand for hook for attention.
You want, you want attention, always, always, always.
So let's just try to see if I can lighten this blue up a little bit.
I don't know why it's doing that. Premier premier's buggy.
Eh, I'm not a big fan of that. Let's try,
I mean, if I change this to red, it's gonna change the game.
It looks really out there,
but sometimes just going traditional black and white actually
feels a little, A little bit better. Um,
all right, I'm just gonna go back to it.
And this is part of that creative process, guys.
When you're editing you, you kind of want to just play around with stuff.
Uh, obviously you can work backwards with a video like this where it's like,
okay, this is clearly something that they're testing.
You can run with that or you can apply something completely different.
Um, what I wanna do here, 'cause I feel like there's so much blue on the screen,
I, I'm gonna just remove that background actually here,
so I can go into the box opacity and remove that background entirely.
And then now it just kind of feels like, you know, it's not,
it's not so in your face about it, right? It's just kind of like,
it's there. So it's almost like there's a curiosity aspect to here.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless.
Why is he eating french fries if he lost weight? There's something very like,
cognizant, like it's, it's, there's like incongruence here.
So that could potentially work as a hook. We, we don't know until we test it.
Um, so now that we've got that,
let's jump into the rest of the video, right? So let's go back to the shot list.
And I'm just gonna like summarize these clips, but, um,
New images helping transform the health of thousands of Americans. This is like,
this is obviously a voiceover, but for caption's sake,
I'm just gonna reduce it to this. Uh, and here I can actually,
I think would be good to just copy and paste or copy the,
the stylization of the, the captions of the titles.
So I'm hitting option or alt boom,
and I'm going to,
so this is gonna be super long, obviously. So we want to split that into two.
Uh, new image is helping transform
the health of da, da, da Americans.
So this would be potentially a good opportunity.
So I'm gonna reduce the font size, obviously. Okay, that looks good. Um,
and I'm gonna do, I'm gonna put the word the up there.
This is a good opportunity to add a, uh, an American flag emoji here.
So this is something that if you haven't done already,
make sure to do it. But, um,
create an emoji library and we have a separate tutorial on that.
But what this does is it takes our entire emoji library, uh,
and puts it into your premiere so you can easily search for emojis without
having to drag and drop them into your timeline.
So I'm just gonna type in American, I'm gonna do,
I'm gonna do flag, maybe u s a Now.
It's not a perfect system, obviously, but it's better than, uh,
better than nothing. So, uh,
from here I'm just gonna click on the flag and I'm gonna drag it into my graphic
spin. Boom. Now I have this emoji and I didn't have to leave,
I didn't have to go anywhere, so, nice. So the next step to this,
and this is what makes this, uh, this plugin, or I'm sorry,
this mo super cool,
is now I can add emojis into here,
any ones that I want on the left or the right side.
So I'm gonna click and drag this into here, and I'm gonna turn it on.
And boom, now I've got myself an American emoji, uh, American flag emoji.
Check that out. Isn't that cool? All right,
perfect.
So one thing that I want to do here is actually you can, you know,
spice it up a little bit. You can rotate this text.
I think there might be even a rotation feature or, yeah, here it is rotation,
which will keep it on the axis right there. So you can do something like that.
Um, so it's not just like, it looks like it's,
it's getting cut off up top. So I want to actually fix that.
So bring it back to center and we'll bring it down
and then rotate, like here. Cool.
Yeah, I like that. So again,
we haven't added any music to this. Um, and that's fine.
It's really your preference if you want to add music,
but sometimes it could be distracting and sometimes it can work. But,
uh, I have a track right here that I was gonna use.
Might as well. Let's just run with it. Um, so it's already in here.
I'm gonna open it up and now I'm gonna drag that into my music bin.
Okay. This is why these bins are very important.
'cause then you can just drag it where it needs to go. Okay?
Boom. All right. So if we want to add music,
let's just throw that underneath here.
It's gonna completely change the video now.
Yeah. 'cause you, you know, there's a beat going on. Um,
so I think with a voiceover, this video would be a lot more, uh, engaging.
So we'll add that later on, because this is not gonna be a voiceover tutorial.
This is more just showing a start to finish video ad.
Another thing we could do too is, um, start the, where the music picks up.
Like right here.
I feel like that's like a good time to,
it's a good opportunity to bring the energy back in, right?
There it is. Yeah. That's what we want.
Boom.
Okay, cool. So right here. And
I, I'm gonna mute the music for now just because it's gonna,
it's going to get in the way tutorial.
So I think there could be an opportunity here to add an extra clip.
Do do, because it's a little boring there. Um,
I could just speed it up to be honest. Um, let's play that.
Okay. So one thing I wanna do actually here is add a a zoom,
just because there's a lot of space, dead space, there's not much happening.
And obviously this is still the, uh, the interest phase.
So we want to keep things visually interesting. So I'm gonna hit, uh,
shift seven as my shortcut to effects. Yeah,
I'm gonna type in scale again, and let's do 1 25. Drag that in.
There we go. That looks a little bit better, right?
Great. I love it. Awesome. Okay.
If you ever get spacing like this,
a real quick shortcut, and you've gotta make sure that there's no,
there's no layers at all, uh, in this entire column right here.
But you just click on it and then click backspace or delete,
and it'll move everything to where you want it to go. All right,
so we've got new images helping transform the health of thousands,
thousands of Americans. Um, and now we want to introduce the product.
So let's go back there. Um, featuring wait lists.
I, I'm just gonna do like, wait list includes da, da, da, da da.
So let's take the same titles here from the
first one and just modify it,
right? And let's see.
I feel like
It is called wait list or featuring wait list, featuring wait list. Yeah,
we can do featuring wait list.
Let's reduce the font size a little bit there.
And I'm gonna move it down like this just so it's a little bit more centered.
Um, and what I actually wanna do, what, what you can do for like, the zoom in.
So if you zoom in here, zoom out from here,
and it kind of gives this cool, like back and forth effect.
So you'll do the opposite. So 1, 1 50 to a hundred, let's try that.
So if you start here, it'll come out.
And I feel like it's a good opportunity when you can zoom in,
you can zoom out just visually more stimulating.
All right, so the next thing I wanna do is actually add bullet points.
I want to add these three, uh, ingredients.
So how I'm gonna do that is very simple. There's actually a few ways,
two ways or so that you can do this. You can do, uh,
you can type in bullets and you can see that we have, uh,
presets already done in terms of like
bullet options. Okay?
Now we have to update these to include the, um,
the upload the emoji aspect.
So once those are updated, then you know, you,
you'll be able to just throw in your,
your benefits right here really quickly. Honestly,
I could probably just use this, he, uh, this whole thing for this ad. But,
um, I just want to show you if you have bullets. This is like,
this is key right here. Let me just,
I can turn this off 'cause I don't need that.
'cause I already have a head headline up there. But
what I like about this is it's all done for you. Uh,
let's move the letter spacing to zero. And it's actually,
oh, so this is actually, we're, we're affecting the headline,
so we don't really need that one.
Let's change the ladder spacing here. Okay.
And let's increase the font size there.
And obviously for any type of like check mark or like list
you want, you know, a plus or like a, a check or a,
some sort of emoji, uh, it, it,
it gives it that more user generated feel.
But let's just go with that first one right there.
I'm not sure if I have that d n a emoji here, so I might,
I might, I might not. Oh, I do. Fantastic. Great. So I did a dropdown.
Eventually this will turn into a upload spot. So that'll be,
and so it shows that, um, I can do either o either side, uh,
of the emoji.
So I'm actually just gonna turn that one off 'cause I don't need it.
And I'm gonna paste my
emoji in there. Or I'm sorry, my text in there. So you got your
font. So right here, I have some options, right? I can,
I can make it branded or I can remove the background entirely if I wanted to.
Let's try making it branded and see what that looks like.
I don't know why. Oh, it's just because the, uh, the yellow,
it is the yellow that's causing that. That's, that's a bummer.
Let's try a different color just because, you know, there's a little bit of,
there's like a lot of blue going on here,
Text color white and
looks okay. Um, it might look nice
because it's like so bright. Um,
we could add a drop shadow to it. Um,
or we can reduce the,
I would say the exposure on this scene a little bit so it pops out a little bit
more. Could do something like that.
Okay,
So let's just finish off the, the rest of those, those bullets.
So, um, these were the same. Let's,
we could basically just follow the same, um,
structure here. Let me just trim this.
Cool. And bullet number two, I don't need this.
I'm gonna do d n a.
Great. And lemme just double check what the settings were here.
So 56.
Yeah, if you're going to, um, adjust the, uh,
the font size, you just wanna make sure you remember it.
I remember this was that. So,
so this is one way of doing it, right?
The other way would be to do these individually and then just
paste them so you don't have to redo the, uh, the,
the stylization. And I can do that really quick too. 'cause I actually,
I sometimes prefer that, prefer that look.
And then I can, um, change the alignment of it as well. 'cause we're,
we're working with,
we're working with the same style throughout the whole video.
Okay.
I don't know what happened there. That was weird. Just these,
these weird medical terms.
Is it 36, man?
I have, uh, 56.
Hmm. Don't mind that color. But
yeah, I think doing it the first way, you know,
if you're gonna do a lot of different colors,
but the thing is that you're gonna get those animations pre-made already, so it,
it really is up to you. Boom. Oh,
I forgot the bit, the benefit and feature to the second one. My b
let's get that in there.
Oh, that's number one. Number two, great.
Cool. All right. Yeah, I'm, I'm, I'm pretty stoked on that.
Let's listen to that with music.
Let's see. All right,
so the music does stop right here.
So it feels like more of a natural cut to like,
I feel like it drags on a little long, right there.
Yeah, let's cut it here.
All right. Remember, you can do this. Backspace.
You know, it's interesting, you know, without the music,
I was still able to kind of keep the tempo, because when you're editing,
you kind of wanna just like,
pretend you have this metronome in the back of your mind. Like,
It just helps you stay on rhythm. So you understand like,
the pacing of something. Like, I'm always just like tapping my foot. It's like,
uh, uh, I don't know if you're musical or not, but, uh, if you are,
just kind of transition the musicality into your video.
Uh, if you're not, just think of yourself like hitting your hand.
1, 2, 3, 4, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1.
Like I would cut right there, right?
I feel like that makes a lot of sense and it actually works out pretty, um,
pretty smoothly with the video.
1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2.
Boom. We're rocking, we're rocking. I'm digging it.
I'm digging it. All right, turn the music off. All right,
so here is when we're gonna do some,
some case studies.
So we have a couple options here. Um,
I'm not gonna include all that text, but let's do something like,
so, you know, going into ads, ORX,
I know we have a review counter right here, which
is really fun. I really enjoy this. Uh, enjoy it. I mean,
I really like using it in our videos, in my videos because it's like a,
it's a counter and, uh, it saves a lot of time.
We also have a ton of like, lots of different reviews,
review styles, or I'm sorry, review,
like review websites. So we have like Amazon,
Trustpilot, things like that. Uh,
for this example, I'm going to do, I'm gonna try this one.
Okay? So I'm gonna show you
what that looks like, right? Okay.
So I could overlay that over the video. Um,
and it'll show all the reviews and stuff, and I can remove the background.
So it just kind of adds like a little bit of an effect over it.
So I'm gonna take this and then paste this in here.
Um,
Lemme try something here. Um,
so I can move this up here if I wanted to. This counter is gonna go,
so one thing that I'll do if it, if it doesn't fit,
is you can speed this whole thing up. You know,
you can just do right click speed duration 200,
and now this thing's gonna speed up more. So,
great. Let me go down and I'm gonna change this.
I'm gonna just remove the background. All right? Bring it all the way down.
Now I can see the, the overlay a little bit more clearly.
Cool.
It might make sense to use this a little bit later on, to be honest. Um,
yeah, it's fine. We'll, we'll,
we'll do it there. It really is preference, right?
So now what we can do is make this look a little cooler so we can change the
star color. Let's try changing it to,
I don't know if they have any on their site reviews wise. Oh, they have greens.
Okay, cool, let's try that.
And this is the tru pilot color. Okay?
So this is the star color. And so honestly, we even have these. So
I just wanted to like show you how quickly it is to add these overlays
without having to do them from scratch, right? That's huge.
And you can get creative with how you want to position it. Um,
I think there's a recent study. Go back here.
Internal study results.
I, yeah,
Right. You know, if I were to take off the all caps,
then I can control this 30 day internal study.
You can change the font size there. Extra bold black,
I think all these are like off white. So
change these back to white, full white.
So another thing you can do here is let's say we
wanted to add maybe this like light blue as a tint
in the background, so it stands out a little bit more.
Change this background color to that. And
you've got that, but, uh, not a big fan of it. Let's try the dark blue.
And of course, you just gotta play with stuff. You gotta see, you know,
how you like it if it looks good. Um,
so you can see there's also a stroke width on here.
This is an opportunity to maybe add a little bit more branding in here.
Okay. You can increase the width or you can remove it entirely.
So sometimes it looks better without it to be honest.
Cool. Okay.
So you can see there's a little ending here where it transitions out. Okay?
So you can take that, cut it,
and then paste it down here where it actually, where the screen ends. So
Something like that.
So one thing I forgot to mention is you can actually change the, the number of,
number of reviews. Okay? So down here
number start right here. Okay, so
starts at one and then ends at 30. So this goes by thousands.
And so if you had more customers,
I mean you could fill this thing up to like a hundred thousand,
or I think it goes up to 999,000, um, anything above that,
then the comma won't, comma won't show.
But you can start it off at like 50000th of the counter does something like
this. Yeah. But it doesn't look as realistic.
So doing something like,
let's just do like 30 and then start at this one.
Cool. All right. So that's an option, guys. This, this doesn't,
this doesn't mean that you need to make it this way. Exactly.
Let me just show you another way of doing this. So let me just hide this. Um,
you know, you can,
you can just go back and then use some of these titles that you previously used.
You can just put that straight in the center there
and throw in that, uh,
throw in those results.
Yeah. So you can't, you can't, um,
stack 'em like that. You have to do two lines
like this. And let's add an emoji to the right side of that.
I'm gonna go here and go to my emojis. Yeah, flex Biceps. Perfect.
Throw that into my graphics panel. I'm gonna go back here.
I'm gonna drag it into the right side. Boom.
And continue that process with that. Cool.
Great. I dig it. I dig it. Alright,
let's save that. And let's finish up the rest of this video.
So we've got closeup of the product, um,
prescription only weight loss.
So I feel like these are options to do bullets.
So let me just push that in there. Prescription only. This is like,
as an editor, you should like look out for ways to just summarize things.
Prescription only weight loss treatment plan developed by
top physicians and pharmacists. Okay, so I'm gonna,
I'm gonna use these as little bullets that come up
and I'm gonna use the same kind of I'm format here. I,
and I'm gonna have them pop up like, so I'm just gonna copy that over.
All right, let's start with the first one, prescription only.
And I'm gonna do custom emojis for each one. Okay.
Prescription only. And I wanna make sure that,
Yeah,
What we can do is let's try taking the box off and
let's try lowering,
reduce the exposure a little bit there. Cool.
Now I want to add,
let's say bottle or like rx. Let's see,
doctor. So if you can't find something, that's fine.
You just gotta go into see if there's a doctor in here,
right? Let's try in doctor,
Doctor
Can also do just a check. I feel like these are really valuable.
I use these all the time and they just,
they just demonstrate the point really quickly. So prescription only
left this time, we're gonna do a left emoji. So boom.
And so if I want to go in here and actually, you know, modify it, I,
I totally can.
So I can make this a little bit smaller and I can move it to the left if I
wanted to, which is just so powerful. I love that so much.
So I'm gonna take this. So just hit shift F five.
I'm gonna move this guy up here
and gonna just basically have these, uh,
titles come out like one at a time, like staggered
prescription only weight loss treatment plan.
And so I'm gonna have it come down.
I am gonna add the second line here, treatment plan.
I'm gonna take off that emoji,
not a huge fan of that, how it, um, kind of overlays like that.
I'd want it like aligned left. So
what I'll do is try to keep everything on one line,
just call it weight loss plan. Okay? Makes it easier to see,
and I can just move it a little bit so it's aligned.
And then lastly, it's,
this is gonna be a really long line. So I would just say like, doctor approved,
physician approved. And
this is for the sake of example only, okay?
Because if you're working with a brand and they,
you can't say certain things, you know, that's gonna be an issue.
So you just wanna make sure you're compliant. You,
so I'm gonna reduce the font size two 80. Yeah, let's do that to all of them.
All right, cool.
So it looks like these guys are a little bit off and that's fine.
It's just like,
so what I wanna do is actually, because there's a lot of space here, um,
I wanted to move these guys around. So weight loss plan,
physician approved, let's see,
ideally I'd want them like,
and then physician approved.
So let's see. I, I, I might be, I,
Here
We go. Yeah, there it goes.
Now we might need to extend that depending on,
I think I can move a little bit, I can add a little bit back into it.
Yeah, I think that'll be fine. Cool.
So I'm gonna trim all that off.
Looks like there's a little gap here
and that's, that's fine.
All right, cool. What's the next step? Is um,
showing X at the pharmacy,
not available in any pharmacy. I'm just gonna add that at the title
and I'm gonna add a big X in there. So let's do that.
And I know that that's called crossmark.
Take that, drag that into my timeline there.
Alright, I'm gonna replace this
actually. Um, I can just use the emoji itself. Okay.
And I'm gonna show you a different way that you can stylize this so
you can add a stroke. All right, so now it looks very,
now it looks even more toy, right?
So let's do not available at any
on the second line, any pharmacy. Great.
Now lemme turn off this and let's increase the font size.
Okay,
lemme change the width, add a little bit more.
Okay, take my cross mark here.
So one thing we have, we have a really cool Mott. Um,
if you go into, if you type in check and crossmark symbols,
it has already animated ones, which I really love 'cause I use these so much.
Let me show you really quick. Um,
but basically it'll animate it for you like that, which is, which is great,
right? And you can toggle between a cross symbol or a check mark,
and then you can, there's different styles. So these are, these are rad,
go to cross symbol and then, you know, check,
choose a style that you want. I'm gonna go style one.
And then you can change the animation too. So, you know,
you can do a scale, you can do a rotation. Love it,
man. So fun. So useful. But for this one,
let's just do a draw.
And I'm gonna actually put these behind the title. So I'll,
I'll make that come out just like that. Boom.
And I'll just cut that. I don't need this anymore.
Cool. Um, what I like to do when like, something is, you know, it says no,
don't do that. I like to just go and change the saturation a little bit,
reduce that saturation. So it's like you're asking on TV style, um,
you know, indicates it's bad. We don't need a, we don't want to go there.
So I'll reduce the saturation. I'll even add a vne, um,
just a little bit just to give it like, some of that depth, like
Yeah,
Then it feels, and it feels like this is the enemy.
You don't want that in our life, right? Cool.
So we're almost done with the video. Lastly,
we just want to get these last steps. Visit website, get prescribed,
receive medication. So, you know, we've done a lot of these,
like individual bop bops, call 'em bop, bops. Um,
but we also have these bullets over here that we can reuse.
So let's just copy that over.
Uh, I can go through and probably check change all these.
Um, let's just do
backhand pointing. Let's change these all to backhand pointing.
'cause these are like steps, right?
Oh, the last one.
All right, cool. So what are the steps? You tell me? Visit website.
Get prescribed, receive medication.
Cool. So bullet one,
visit website. Cool, that one's done.
Get prescribed. Oops, I forgot. Number two,
get prescribed
number one, visit website. And then lastly is receive meds.
Receive those meds. Two, three,
I am gonna call it meds, eh, keeping medication.
So one thing you could do here, you can change the roundness of all of the, the,
uh,
around the actual titles. One thing that, um,
we'll probably work on is getting like a master one,
which will update each one automatically. So,
Cool. I'm actually gonna speed that up.
I feel like that could probably be done faster,
just so the steps come in sooner.
I,
All right, cool. So, you know,
there's a few things you can do here. If you wanted,
you can put the titles up there. You can bring 'em down here.
You can add a bar around here and show the step. But,
you know, let me see here.
Maybe zoom in a little bit because there's a lot of dead space. Uh,
yep.
Just like that.
Cool. And then lastly, see,
see if waitlist is right for you. You know,
this is like a last call to action right here.
Let's do what other styles we got. We got this one,
so let's bring that one back.
I will split those lines. Cool.
All right. I'm stoked. It kinda looks like he's naked.
So I'm gonna move the titles down here
and I'm gonna add a scale, just 'cause I feel like it's needed here.
Great. And lastly, you know, you just put the logo, I would do like a logo,
uh, c t a. So you can do something like this where there are templates.
You can find the one to the nine by 16. Find your aspect ratio
and boom, I've got this one right here. So let's pop that in there.
Boom.
And then I'd probably cut it there 'cause the music actually works out
perfectly.
All right, perfect. So lastly,
then we can just update this to include all those, those assets in there.
So let me just double check. I've got the, uh, the logo here.
Get that bad boy placed in here
into my graphics spin. Cool.
Now this is a C t A, it's really awesome. It has all the, you know,
presets you need. Let's pop in that logo,
replace ours with a new image. So if this ever happens,
just scale it down a little bit. Okay?
Scale it down scale to fit. You can do that. Um,
and then you can actually scale the logo like this.
Boom. Awesome. Okay, product settings.
We've got a product, let's go get it on their website.
Open image and new tab. All right, so this is gonna be,
this could be an issue unless we change the background. That's fine. Let's, uh,
product image. All right,
bring that into our timeline.
Graphics. Cool. Drag it in.
Boom. Oh, it's actually p and g. Perfect. So let's actually,
great. It's funny, it says prescriptions.
It's actually weight loss prescriptions. Um, all right,
so we've got the product. I'm happy with how that looks.
Now we've got the badge, which is this guy right here, the 25% off.
Now I don't know if they're offering any bundle deals, but you know,
if you wanted to change this, you can,
or you can omit it or you can remove it entirely. Uh, in this case,
I'm gonna remove it and I'm actually gonna move the product over to the right.
So let's just do that. So it's nice and centered.
Yeah, there we go.
And now I can actually scale this guy so I can move it
here as well. A little faster. Great,
I'm digging that. So next we've got the product settings,
batch things. We're good. Tech settings. All right,
so now we've just gotta include some website copy your three in one
weight loss medication. It's very generic here.
Um, it would probably be more like,
let's see,
try
prescribed wait list today.
And then I would probably move this guy. Oops, move this copy down below.
I
See if you qualify. Obviously there's, there's a lot of potentials here.
Text settings. Let's go down, change this to three one,
weight loss medication prescription only. You know,
there's a lot of potentials here.
Or you can do like click link below.
This could be a more direct call to action.
Click link to see if you qualify, right?
That's nice. Thank you. Cool.
I'm happy with how that looks. Now,
which just comes down to the background setting.
So we've got the stroke up here, which could be used.
We can probably maybe add some branding in there.
That looks cool. Now we've got the stroke number two, which is down,
down below. I think we might be able to keep that. But here's, uh,
here's the actual background. So we can do a gradient. Um,
let's see what they have on their site.
Looks like they have a gradient here from this color to that. So let's try,
let's try it.
This goes from light to dark. So light to
to dark. Okay,
now let's do dark here. Whoops,
not bad. Let's see. Okay, so if I move this
Gradient, it might, it can change the way it looks. That looks kind of cool.
Now, obviously the, um, the logo settings here,
what we can do is actually change it all to white, which is super,
super convenient. If you click on this button, boom, it'll change that for you.
You don't have to do anything. I love that so much.
And let's scale this down a little bit more. And there you go guys.
Okay, so this asset right here,
you can convert that into an MP four and reuse that over and over again.
You don't have to like, recreate that each time, especially if you're,
if you're working with the brand. Um, so boom. And look,
it looks like there's like a little bit of a, a delay here,
so I'm just gonna trim that off. So,
or what I could do is just move that under, under the shot.
But no, I'm just gonna trim it off. There's a little bit of a lag.
Boom. There it is, guys. There it is.
And it looks like there's a little bit of an off center on the product right
here. I'll move that. But other than that, I think that looks fantastic.
And so let's play it through one more time and I'll put my ED point here.
I'll do out for end start, start over.
Let see. It's lacking a little bit.
Boom,
22nd add, there we go. And that's one style, one variation, one hook,
right? All of these individual clips could be modified,
could be interchanged, because we modularized everything. Um,
and yeah,
I think that's a pretty solid video that doesn't even have a voiceover onto it.
Uh, that'll completely change the video if we add a voiceover. But this is, uh,
I would say, um,
I think the only thing I would do here would be probably split up these lines,
um,
just because I felt like there wasn't anything happening on the screen too much.
So I was gonna
take this line out and then add a second
in their first 30 days and then kind of separate these two lines like
that, just so,
and it actually works out with the music. I even expect that
like, it, the music actually goes. So if you wanted,
you could do like a third caption. You can do something like,
lemme move this. I don't need this adjustment layer. That's not necessary.
So
right here,
and then I'm gonna change this to like in a recent study,
internal, uh, wait lists
on average
Do
Patient patience.
So let's change the font size there.
Okay, so I'm gonna take,
yeah, see that looks pretty cool. Um,
I can even try something like this.
So there's a little bit more of a variety in the colors.
Change the color font black here. Yep.
Okay,
Click.
Okay. So that's actually where the drop hits. So I want to move that title here.
Cool. Loving it, dig it.
All right, fantastic. Honestly, that's probably, uh,
a worthy video to the client. Um,
so let's see where we're at.
So we've got the ad styles, we added the titles, the overlay, the music,
the effects. You know, obviously if I wanted,
I could probably go in there a little bit more, um,
and fix or like added any more effects. But, uh, for a U G C like this,
I really don't think it's necessary. Zoom ins and zoom outs are,
are usually most effective. You know, we, we could do a small,
like a very slight, um, linear one here, like a small zoom in.
It's very, very not that noticeable. All we can do maybe one here.
Yeah, what happens is we kinda lose him flexing, right?
Which isn't bad. No. Looks great.
Cool. Now, color correction, um,
for this video honestly doesn't really need too much of it because it's U G C.
Um, the shots are already kind of like already there,
but the color correction that I typically go with, you know,
I'll do an adjustment layer across the whole video and then just maybe add a
little bit. Let's go into that real quick.
So have an adjustment layer,
And I'll go into here
and then go into the basic correction here. And I'm just playing with the, um,
you know, depending on what the video needs especially. Okay, so this is a hook,
right? So we want this to, to really stand out.
We can maybe even jack up the saturation there.
You see what a difference that made it look.
So you can do something like that, or you can desaturate it, right? Like
now it, now it looks very like pale. Um,
very similar to that pain point we had. You know,
if you add a little bit of a vignette to it,
it just turns into a completely different look and feel.
So that's one,
I would say one adjustment layer that you can do for the, for the hook.
Now it looks more cinematic and a more epic. But here, you know,
if I wanted to brighten up this video a little bit more, um,
make it stand out, I,
I typically just go by eye. Um,
I'll go here and I'll add a little bit of vibrance to it,
just to give it a little bit more life, uh, because let's see,
without it, so yeah, there's just a little bit,
a little bit of a difference there.
Yeah,
The blacks are a little bit more, um, more pronounced.
Bring
The blacks down. Cool.
Yeah. So let's see the before and after.
I
Probably tone it down a little bit here.
Let's see. Let's bring this guy down.
Yeah, I'm happy with that. You know, it's, it's, it's minor, but it's not,
doesn't need to be too much.
This one already did add a color correction to that. Um,
maybe drag this over, see if it makes a difference.
I think it looks better without it,
but we can add it to this shot at the end if we wanted to.
All right, sweet. Perfect. And there you go.
Now we've got ourselves a a little bit of color correction. Like I said,
we don't want to go too heavy on it. We just wanna bring out some of the,
the contrast and the vibrance, because it's kind of a dull, uh,
iPhone footage can sometimes be dull. Um,
and then for the hooks and pain points, like we just want to either desaturate,
add vignettes, make them a little bit more dramatic. Um,
and then what we'll do next is go over. Um,
so in this video,
we're not gonna go over subtitles or audio levels because it's already kind of
pre-done, but, um,
next we're gonna go over hook variations. So actually before we finish off,
let me just show you, um, how I like to do my audio.
So for a song like this,
you know, it's already peaking at like, at like zero. Um,
this isn't bad or anything, but if you go into your audio track mix right here,
okay? Um, and especially if you have a lot of different audio clips happening,
like a voiceover and stuff like that, you wanna set limiters.
So if you click on this dropdown, this is like hidden. So this is under the,
the audio track mixer. All right, so boom,
we've got that guy going on. So click on that dropdown, and then these are your,
I believe these are your bus, these are called buses,
but you can set one on the master. But if you click on this,
you can see that there's all these different effects that you can do to your
sound. It's almost like if you're doing any type of like, audio, audio work.
But, um, like I said, I like to use this.
If I have a lot like voiceovers happening or sound effects,
then I can control more of the audio. But in this case, it's just music,
so it doesn't really matter too much. But, um, you can add a limiter here,
which is if you go to a amplitude and compression,
go to hard limiter and then double click on that, uh,
move my face, it'll come up with this option. And then maximum amplitude, um,
keep this at like negative six.
This will kind of keep everything from turning red. Um,
and it's gonna be like right down here.
And if you wanted to input everything on the tracks by like five decibels or
like 10, if everything's really low, you can do that all at one time.
So that's really helpful. Um,
so you don't have to go in there and individually control everything.
This will do all of your audio tracks, but if you do want to, uh,
add this to an individual track,
all you gotta do is hit all option or all drag this over, and, uh,
it'll basically apply the same settings over there and you can remove this if
you wanted to. Um, but I, you know, uh,
for this example, it doesn't make sense to have, you know,
limiter because you only have one audio, uh, one audio piece.
But yeah, anyways, I would say this video is almost done.
I think the next step is just finishing off the hook variations and then it's
off to the races. All right, guys, thanks for joining me on this,
and I hope you learned a lot. I'll see you in the next one.